<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Paul Stanfield</title>
 <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/"/>
 <updated>2014-10-08T18:31:43+01:00</updated>
 <id>http://paulstanfield.co.uk</id>
 <author>
   <name>Paul Stanfield</name>
   <email>hello@paulstanfield.co.uk</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>New Things, New Blog</title>
   <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/08/new-things-new-blog-post/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/08/new-things-new-blog-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Like most people who have a keen interest in something whether it be in their work or personal life, the notion of ‘Why don’t I start a blog?’ often creeps to mind once a while without ever leading to any real end product. Recently I’ve been toying with this idea back and forth with the usual negative concerns associated with it of &quot;Will I post regularly?&quot;, &quot;Is it really worth the hassle?&quot; etc etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of focusing on the things which inevitably hold us back from doing things, I’ve decided to get of the sofa from playing another round of video games and actually start the blog, it might not lead to anything, but you’ll never know where something will go unless you give it a fair old try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here’s the blog! its up, its running, it lives on the internet! So far so good I’d say, no?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been trying to be more productive in my life and change a few things up, whether it be taking on more design work both in a freelance and personal capacity, getting more exercise, reading more books etc. Just little bits and pieces to ultimately try and gain a better and happier life during the working week and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully this blog will give you a bit of an insight into that and maybe allow me to share some of things I’ll hopefully learn along the way, enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
