<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Paul Stanfield</title>
 <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/"/>
 <updated>2014-10-12T18:42:49+01:00</updated>
 <id>http://paulstanfield.co.uk</id>
 <author>
   <name>Paul Stanfield</name>
   <email>hello@paulstanfield.co.uk</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Top Work Related iPhone Apps</title>
   <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/13/top-work-related-iphone-apps/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/13/top-work-related-iphone-apps</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The iPhones great for checking the ridiculous amount of social media accounts people have, consuming all those viral youtube videos and checking out the latest addictive game that has taken the App Store by storm. I also use my iPhone quite heavily to keep on top of things in my working life, whether that be gaining inspiration for the next design project or keeping on top of my freelance business. Check out some of the app’s that are currently helping me along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Things&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With multiple projects on the go and different tasks being associated with them at varying deadline dates a simple to do list app just isn’t cutting it for me. Things solves this problem by allowing me to make detailed project lists and notes for all things relating to a project. I’ve tried out a few apps like this in the past but Things ticks all the boxes in terms of price, usability and iCloud syncing. Having it on my home screen on my iPhone gives me a constant reminder of what needs done and with the added refresh to the UI and increased use of notifications that has just been rolled out for iOS 8, the app has just got a whole lot better!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/things1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/things2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/en/app/things/id284971781?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Things out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chrome&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a while now I have liked to keep two browsers on the go at all times for various tasks. I don’t know a lot of people who do this but it suits my workflow perfectly. I keep Safari dedicated to my personal browsing, be that Facebook, SkySports News, MacRumours, Youtube etc and then use Google Chrome as my dedicated browser for all things work related. This allows me to stay focused on the task at hand during the working day without being distracted by open tabs which may cause a distraction. This works a treat on the desktop with two different browser windows running at the same time being a piece of cake, I like to bring this experience over to the iPhone for quick referral on links and accounts, so Google Chrome’s iOS browser app does the job perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/chrome1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/chrome2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/chrome-web-browser-by-google/id535886823?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Chrome out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Up until quite recently finding a decent iPhone app to track website analytics was a bit of nightmare, with most on the App Store being buggy and with poor UI. Thankfully though Google finally released their own official analytics app which brings all the joy of their web app over to iOS. The app does exactly what it says on the tin and works a treat!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/analytics1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/analytics2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/google-analytics/id881599038?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Google Analytics out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Facebook Pages Manager&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I currently use this handy wee app to keep on track of the Facebook pages I am currently working on for both personal and freelance work. The app allows a simple and elegant way to manage pages which is a lot less fiddly than trying to manage them via the standard Facebook app. The pages version also brings to the table a lot of handy features tailored to your Facebook page such as analytics and quick links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/pages1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/pages2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/facebook-pages-manager/id514643583?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Facebook Pages Manager out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Buffer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buffer is a great app for keeping on top of your social media presence, allowing you to schedule posts for your social media accounts in order to share content with your followers. I predominately use it for its Twitter integration at the moment and find it extremely handy on the go when an idea for a post comes to mind which you might want to send out later on in the day, Buffer to the rescue!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/buffer1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/buffer2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/buffer-for-social-media-twitter/id490474324?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Buffer out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Ember&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use Ember for Mac extensively for inspiration, gathering and research, it acts as my main information hub and go to for kicking off new projects and for those annoying moments when creative block kicks in. The iOS app from Ember brings this experience over to the iPhone and is a great little tool to have out and about for those gems of inspiration you come across which you want to quickly save to your library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/ember1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/ember2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href= https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/ember-screenshot-annotate/id478308340?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Ember out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Freeshot&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a new one to my collection as I try to get more active on the Dribbble community. Freeshot allows me to keep track of how my latest shots are doing and the feedback they have received as well as acting as a nice way to gain a dose of design inspiration in those moments of down time standing in queues and on the daily commute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/freeshot1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/oct14/freeshot2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/gb/app/freeshot-dribbble-client/id713708907?mt=8&quot;&gt;Check Freeshot out on the App Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>New Things, New Blog</title>
   <link href="http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/08/new-things-new-blog-post/"/>
   <updated>2014-10-08T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://paulstanfield.co.uk/2014/10/08/new-things-new-blog-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Like most people who have a keen interest in something whether it be in their work or personal life, the notion of ‘Why don’t I start a blog?’ often creeps to mind once a while without ever leading to any real end product. Recently I’ve been toying with this idea back and forth with the usual negative concerns associated with it of &quot;Will I post regularly?&quot;, &quot;Is it really worth the hassle?&quot; etc etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of focusing on the things which inevitably hold us back from doing things, I’ve decided to get of the sofa from playing another round of video games and actually start the blog, it might not lead to anything, but you’ll never know where something will go unless you give it a fair old try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here’s the blog! its up, its running, it lives on the internet! So far so good I’d say, no?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been trying to be more productive in my life and change a few things up, whether it be taking on more design work both in a freelance and personal capacity, getting more exercise, reading more books etc. Just little bits and pieces to ultimately try and gain a better and happier life during the working week and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully this blog will give you a bit of an insight into that and maybe allow me to share some of things I’ll hopefully learn along the way, enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
